So now we've modified our get_next_target procedure,
我们已经修改了 get_next_target (寻找下一目标) 过程
and it will return None as the first output if there's no next target.
如果没有下一目标 程序就返回 None (无) 这是第一个输出
Otherwise it will return the URL and the end_quote.
否则 就返回 URL (网址) 和 end_quote (结束引用)
And now all we have to do is figure out how to keep going.
现在我们要做的是让程序继续运行
Let's look at what we were doing before.
先来看看我们之前所做的
We turned these 4 lines into our procedure
我们将这4行代码变成了一个过程
so now we can--instead of having all this code,
所以 现在我们就不用再写一遍这些代码
we're going to call the get_next_target
而是可以直接调用 get_next_target
and assign the results.
并赋值结果
Now we've got the value of URL, which we do on a print out,
我们已经有 URL 的值 并且想将其打印出来
so we're still going to print that out as before.
现在我们仍然会将其打印出来
And we still want to update the value of page,
而且我们仍然想要更新页面的值
but we don't want to use end_quote now.
但我们不想使用 end_quote 了
What we want to use is the value that was returned here,
我们想用的是这里返回的值
which we assigned to the variable endpos.
也就是我们赋给变量 endpos (结束位置) 的值
And then, well, we're doing it all again.
接下来 我们再来一遍
So, all of the code here is just another call to get_next_target,
这里的所有代码就是再次调用 get_next_target
and similarly, this would be endpos instead of end_quote.
同样的 这里应该是 endpos 而不是 end_quote
And we want to keep going until we get to the end,
我们想一直继续到结束
so how do we decide when we've gotten to the end?
但什么时候才是结束呢？
Well, we got to the end when the URL
当返回的 URL 是 none 时
that's returned is None.
就是结束
And when the call to get_next_target returns None for the URL,
当调用的 get_next_target 返回 none
we know we're done.
我们就知道 程序结束了
We've seen a way to keep going. That's a while loop.
让程序继续的一种方式就是 while 循环
We've seen a way to do a test.
我们知道如何做判断
We want to test the URL.
我们想要判断 URL
And we have everything we need now to print all the links on the page.
要打印页面上的所有链接 我们已经掌握了所需的全部知识
I'm going to give you a start for how to write this procedure,
我会开个头 教你们如何写这个程序
and then you're going to finish it.
之后你们就自己完成
What we're going to do is define a procedure
我们将定义一个过程
that will print all the links on the page,
打印出页面上的所有链接
and it takes the page as input, and so we want to use a while loop to keep going,
输入为该页面 我们想用一个 while 循环来让程序持续运行
and I am going to leave blank the test condition for the while loop.
我将把 while 循环的判断条件留为空白
We'll leave that as something for you to figure out.
由你们去填
In the body of the while loop, what we're going to call get_next_target,
在 while 循环的主体语句中 我们将调用 get_next_target
assigning URL and endpos to the result.
将 URL 和 endpos 赋值给结果
This is just like what we were doing in the example code.
这和我们之前示范的代码是一样的
Now what we need to do is check whether we got a valid URL,
现在我们要做的是 检查是否有一个有效 URL
so what we were doing here,
这就是这一块要做的事情
we assumed that we always got a valid URL,
假设我们总是有一个有效 URL
and we printed it out, and we kept going, but we need to do something to test
我们将其打印出来 程序继续运行
whether the URL that we got back is None.
但是我们还需要判断 我们得到的 URL 是否是 None
That's what we'll do.
这就是我们将要做的
We have if URL, and if that's true, that means we found a valid URL.
这里是 if URL 如果为真 就意味着我们找到了一个有效 URL
We didn't get the value None as the result from get_next_target.
从 get_next_target 得到的结果不是 none
And so we want to print that out as we were doing before.
那么和之前一样 我们想将其打印出来
We'll print the URL, and we'll advance the page
我们将打印这个 URL 并继续搜索余下内容
to the next position.
直到下一个位置
If we didn't get a valid URL,
如果我们没找到有效 URL
that means that get_next_target did not find a link.
这意味着 get_next_target 没有找到链接
There were no more links on the page,
页面上没有更多链接了
and we need to do something else, and I will leave blank
那我们就要做点别的什么
what we need to do here.
我在这里也留一个空
So, this is all we need for the code to print_all_links.
这就是 print_all_links (打印所有链接) 所需要的全部代码
There are 2 parts left for you to do as the quiz here.
有两处空白是要你们去填的
See if you can figure out what should go as the test condition for the while
看你们是否能想出 while 的判断条件
and in the block for the else.
以及 else 的程序块
And if that's correct, you'll be able to print all the links on the page.
如果你们写对了 就可以打印出页面上的所有链接